<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>   
    <title>Pulley and Rope</title>
    <atom:link href="http://pulleyandrope.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <link>http://pulleyandrope.com</link>
    <description>What it is?!</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <generator>The mighty Wintersmith</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Pulley and Rope</title>
      <link>http://pulleyandrope.com/articles/begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pulleyandrope.com/articles/begin/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;And so we begin&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I purchased this domain name on a whim, with no prior googling to see if the url had a meme attached to it. I bought my server space also on a whim, so, here we are, on the internet, you and me, interacting in a way previously unplanned.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I spent a small amount of time at with people from &lt;a href=&quot;http://braininterfacelab.wordpress.com&quot; title=&quot;hack a brain&quot;&gt;Brain Interface Labs&lt;/a&gt; at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://braininterfacelab.wordpress.com/2013/02/08/hack-a-brain/&quot; title=&quot;hack a brain&quot;&gt;hack a brain&lt;/a&gt; event. It was particularly interesting and got me wondering about the theraputic potentials of a brain interface device. Had a hard day? Stare at these pretty lights for a bit with this headset on. Just wait and see what happens.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, I&apos;m attempting to use the fancy &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/darwin/cmx.js&quot; title=&quot;cmx.js github&quot;&gt;cmx.js&lt;/a&gt; project to start a comic blog at &lt;a href=&quot;http://iwaspromisedcookies.com&quot; title=&quot;I was promised cookies&quot;&gt;iwaspromisedcookies.com&lt;/a&gt; to document the crazy conversations I tend to overhear in New York City. Hopefully, I&apos;ll be able to keep it up ;)

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blog is powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jnordberg.github.com/wintersmith/&quot; title=&quot;wintersmith on github&quot;&gt;Wintersmith&lt;/a&gt;, btw. It is a static page generator built on nodejs and its amazing and I love it so far.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulley and Rope</title>
      <link>http://pulleyandrope.com/articles/dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pulleyandrope.com/articles/dinner/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;h1&gt;Dinner&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This evening began with wine and pasta at our favorite Italian restaurant in Park Slope. The space filled up quickly, so another couple was seated right next to us, in a fashion that would usually be reserved for groups of people that actually know each other.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It must have been a little awkward for them to be seated so closely to another couple that was clearly in the middle of random and empty couple talk. As we chatted about our future plans, goofy work stories, and friend gossip, it became apparent that the other couple was not only listening in to our conversation but talking about and making fun of it. They were making snotty remarks about our wine fueled chitchat not even six inches away from us leading us to wonder if it was possible, that after one glass of wine, were we the loud talking assholes or were they.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will never know.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>